(Sheldon:)Uh, I enjoy some French
toast with butter and syrup.
(Sheldon:)Uh, then a wormhole opens,
(Sheldon:)and whisks me millions of years
(Sheldon:)into the future where
my towering intellect
(Sheldon:)is used to save the last
remnants of mankind
(Sheldon:)from a predatory alien race.
(Penny:)Interesting,
you didn't mention Amy.
(Sheldon:)Who do you think made the French
toast with butter and syrup?
(Woman in lab coat:)You're about to enter the lab
(Woman in lab coat:)of the late Dr. David Saltzberg.
(Woman in lab coat:)While conducting studies
on slowing
(Woman in lab coat:)the aging process, there was
a catastrophic accident
(Woman in lab coat:)and he died.
(Woman in lab coat:)Or did he?
(Leonard:)Ladies?
(Emily:)Are you being polite or scared?
(Penny:)Yup.
(Emily:)Ah, what a room!
Oh-oh!
Oh!
(Leonard:)This is cool.